LOGIN

LOGIN

PRIVACY POLICY

Tranquiliti privacy notice

References to “Tranquiliti”, “we” “us and “our” in this privacy notice are references to Tranquiliti Limited of 15 Queen Square, Leeds, LS2 8AJ  

Our contact details  
  
Tranquiliti Limited is registered at 15 Queen Square, Leeds, LS2 8AJ  
Email: [gdpr@tranquiliti.co](mailto:gdpr@tranquiliti.co?subject=GDPR%20-%20Tranquiliti%20website)  
Web address: [www.tranquiliti.co](http://www.tranquiliti.co/)  
  
Main point of contact for data protection matters: **George Metcalfe**  

The purpose of this document  
  
This privacy notice is written to help individuals understand how Tranquiliti collects and processes personal data, and what rights our data subjects have over what happens to their data, what data we process and how we collect it.  
‍  
Under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), personal data is “any information related to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’)”. The data we collect can be put into the following areas:  
  
**Wellbeing data - obtained from students through our web and mobile app**  
Processing students’ wellbeing data is integral to the delivery of Tranquiliti, and the support we provide to schools and students through our app and dashboard.  
  
**Login data - obtained from students and staff when signing up**  
We process student and staff data around their personal characteristics in order so that we can build a secure login process for all of our users.  
  
**Usage data - obtained when students and staff use Tranquiliti**  
We process anonymised data around how students and staff use our app and dashboard so that we can make improvements to the service and increase our overall impact.  
  
**School data - obtained directly from schools on their students and staff**  
We process school data in order to create a seamless and secure implementation and sign-up process for students and staff, and to help schools better understand their students.  
  
**Marketing data - obtained from our website, other public sources of information, and direct communication**  
We process data on the individuals who are likely to be interested in either purchasing Tranquiliti, or working with us in its development and growth. We also use cookies when people visit our website to help improve their experience, and to make sure we can effectively communicate with them.  

Why do we process this personal data  
  
We process personal data in order to sell our service to schools, and in order so that school staff and students can securely access our digital products, with the overall aim of supporting the wellbeing and education of young people.  

What we do with the data  
‍  
We use data for multiple purposes, all of which contribute to the aim of supporting the wellbeing and education of young people, these include:● Providing school students with personalised support for their wellbeing  
● Providing school staff with insights into the wellbeing of students  
● Ensuring the smooth running of the service, and the sharing of data with the right individuals  
● Identifying how to make improvements to the service based on current usage  
● Identifying and communicating with individuals who may want to use or work with Tranquiliti  

Who we share data with  
  
We share students’ wellbeing data with their schools so that they can proactively support their students. We also share anonymised data with trusted organisations, including charities and universities, who can advance their research using the information.  
  
The only other circumstance in which we will share personal information is when there is a legal requirement to do so.  

How we store your information, and when we delete it  
  
All the data we collect is securely stored within Amazon Web Services.  
  
We store data until it is no longer useful in providing our service. We delete data on our users either when they move on from the relevant school, or when Tranquiliti’s contract with that school ends. We will continue to process anonymised data on users after this point, so that we can continue to carry out analytics on the data to support the improvement of the service.  

Data protection rights  
  
Under data protection law, our data subjects have the following rights:  
**Right of access -** You have the right to ask us for copies of your personal information.  
**Right to rectification -** You have the right to ask us to correct information you think is wrong. You also have the right to ask us to complete information you think is incomplete.  
**Right to erasure -** You have the right to ask us to erase your personal information in certain circumstances.  
**Right to restriction of processing -** You have the right to ask us to restrict the processing of your information in certain circumstances.  
**Right to object to processing -** You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data in certain circumstances.  
**Right to data portability -** You have the right to ask that we transfer the information you gave us to another organisation, or to you, in certain circumstances.  
  
You are not required to pay any charge for exercising your rights. If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. Contact us at [hello@tranquiliti.co](mailto:hello@tranquiliti.co?subject=Data%20Protection%20Rights%20-%20Tranquiliti%20website) or 15 Queen Square, Leeds, LS2 8AJ, if you wish to make a request.  
‍  
  
Changes to this privacy notice  
‍  
If we update this Privacy Notice in a way that significantly changes how we use personal information, we will make sure that we bring these changes to the attention of our data subjects.  

How to complain  
  
You can complain to the ICO if you are unhappy with how we have used your data.  
  
The ICO’s address:  
Information Commissioner’s Office  
Wycliffe House, Water Lane  
Wilmslow, Cheshire  
SK9 5AF  
  
Helpline number: 0303 123 1113  
  
‍  
Our contact details  
  
Tranquiliti Limited is registered at 15 Queen Square, Leeds, LS2 8AJ  
Email: [gdpr@tranquiliti.co](mailto:gdpr@tranquiliti.co?subject=GDPR%20-%20Tranquiliti%20website)  
Web address: [www.tranquiliti.co](http://www.tranquiliti.co/)  
  
Main point of contact for data protection matters: **George Metcalfe**

company registration #11136500

INFO

SOCIAL

ADDRESS

Tes, 70 Gray's Inn Road  
London, WC1X 8NH    
United Kingdom
